# **DAVID MCGREGOR**

#### **Full Stack Developer**

github.com/davmcgregor



# **ABOUT ME**

I'm a full-stack software developer currently working remotely with an emphasis on front end web development. With two years of experience in small and large companies, my love of coding has grown from an interest to a full-fledged passion. Now I'm focused on working with teams to build quality technology and expanding my programming knowledge at every opportunity.

# **RECENT PROJECTS**

#### % Rich Pulse

React, Redux, Tailwind CSS

Concept "Rich List" dashboard site. Experimenting with data visualisation using Chart.js and React Table. Styled with responsive TailwindCSS.

#### % Hiit Workout Generator

React, Redux, Tailwind CSS

App that creates a list of random exercises and provides a countdown timer with sounds. Built using Redux to keep fit while the gyms are closed for COVID-19.

### % Stoic Wisdom

PostgreSQL, Express, React, Node, TailwindCSS

Website and API that showcases quotes from the great stoic thinkers. Additional features include natural language processing, full-text search, and Mailgun integration.

### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

### Junior Front End Developer

#### **Vodafone UK**

**♀** London/Remote

Building the eCare Reinvent Vertical in React as part of the UK Web Engineering team. Collaborating with large teams using agile/scrum workflow, and conducting rigorous testing and reviews of all code.

### Front End Developer

#### **Percipio**

May 2020 - Jan 2021

**♀** London/Remote

Building websites and apps for UK Education and Government Technology sectors, contributing to the development team and implementing UX and information design.

### Digital Communications Specialist (Various Roles)

₩ Jun 2014 - Ongoing

**♀** Sydney/Melbourne/Brisbane

# **TECH SKILLS**

React Native Vue React TypeScript Node.is **Express** Next.js Redux MobX GraphQL Ruby Rails Tailwind CSS Docker **PostgreSQL** MongoDB APIs **AWS** Azure DevOps Heroku Git Workflow Agile Methodology Pair Programming Test-driven Development

### CERTIFICATIONS

The Complete React Native + Hooks Course [2020 Edition]

**Udemy course by Stephen Grider** 

₩ 2020

React Native v0.62.2 with Hooks, Context, and React Navigation

MERN Stack Front to Back

**Udemy course by Brad Traversy** 

₩ 2020

Full Stack React, Redux and Node.js

# **EDUCATION**

Software Developer Graduate

**Makers Academy** 

m Dec 2019 - Mar 2020

Selective 16-week coding course on software engineering fundamentals.

**Juris Doctor** 

The University of Melbourne

max Jan 2010 - Mar 2013

Law Degree - admitted to practice 2015

**Bachelor of Commerce** 

The University of Sydney

m Jan 2007 - Dec 2009

Majors in Economics and International Business